arbys.com 2019-12-09

# Arby's | Privacy Policy

Effective Date 12/1/15

Welcome

This Privacy Policy is designed to explain Arby’s Restaurant Group, Inc. (“Arby’s”) on-line information practices in connection with our arbys.com web site (the “Site”) including the mobile optimized version of our Site. The Privacy Policy describes how Arby’s collects, uses and shares personally identifiable information (“PII”) and other “non-PII” obtained from and about individuals who visit this Site. By using this Site you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy If you do not agree, please do not provide any personal information on the Site.

The Internet presents an opportunity for us to reach our audience in new and exciting ways with product information, company information, and activities such as sweepstakes, contests and other promotions.

## Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used

Personally Identifying Information (“PII”)

This Site is intended to provide a unique and entertaining experience for users. We do not require users to register or submit PII in order to visit the Site and most activities on the Site can be performed without supplying PII.

Arby’s gathers PII, such as first and last names, addresses and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, PII may be collected when you sign up to receive deals and exclusive offers on our Site. In addition, when you visit our Site, we may ask to collect information about your location using technologies such as GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. Arby’s uses this information for location-based services such as locating nearby Arby’s restaurants or identifying special offers that may be of interest to you. When you visit our Site, you may choose not to allow Arby’s to use your physical location. If you would like us to delete location information we have collected, please contact us at the email or postal address listed below. Please note that the Site may not function properly following deletion and that we may be required by law to retain certain information.

We may use PII in sweepstakes, contests or promotional activities, including:  
• to register you for those activities, to verify that you comply with the published rules and to notify you if you are a winner;  
• for coupon, premium or prize delivery;  
• to publicize the names and, where applicable, likenesses of winners;  
• for notification of special offers; and  
• to ensure that we comply with applicable laws.  

The PII you disclose for these and similar activities may be shared with third parties, such as those who may administer the activity for us and shipping companies who may deliver a prize or premium. We will inform you at the time we are collecting the PII that such collection is a requirement for participation.

We may also use your PII for the following purposes:  
• to personalize and enhance our Site and your Site experience;  
• to send you personalized information about our Site via email;  
• to send you advertising or promotional material from us, our advertisers or business partners; and  
• to contact you for feedback regarding us, our advertisers or business partners.  

Should you respond to a particular offer sent on behalf of our business partners or advertisers, we may also use your PII to provide a report to our advertisers or business partners that tells them who responded to a particular offer. Similarly, if you accept an offer contained in an email, we may provide the advertiser or business partner with the PII necessary to fulfill that offer.

Should any of our business partners or advertisers request your PII for their direct use in advertising or marketing (i.e., when the contact with you would come from them and not from us on their behalf), you will always be given the opportunity to remove yourself from the list.

Your PII may also be shared with those persons or entities that administer our Site. Your PII will only be shared with administrators, business partners or advertisers for a particular purpose, and they will not be permitted to use it for any unauthorized purpose.

We may also collect PII to protect your security or ours, to protect us against liability, or to comply with applicable law. PII collected for such reasons will not be used for any other purpose.

Aggregated Information

We may aggregate and use your PII in non-identifiable form for our internal purposes or to share with third parties for any lawful purpose, without your permission. No third party will know who you are as a result of the use of this aggregated information.

Opting-Out

From time to time and as required by law, we may give you the opportunity to “opt-out” of or “opt-in” to particular types of uses or disclosures of PII. If you opt-out of a specific use, we will not use your PII for that purpose.

If you wish to change your decision to “opt-out” or “opt-in,” you can email us at [websupport@arbys.com](mailto:websupport@arbys.com).

Safety and Security

Arby’s takes steps to help ensure that all information provided by you, whether PII or non-PII, is treated securely. No data transmission over the Internet, however, can be guaranteed to be totally secure. While we try to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. You use the Site, and provide us with PII, at your own risk.

## Gathering Information Electronically

Use of Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to enhance your experience on our Site. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Users may have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of the full features of the Site.

Web Beacons

Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites. We may use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our Site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Site. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We may also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send to determine whether you have opened those e-mails or clicked on links in the e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is not personally identifying.

Do-Not-Track

Currently, our servers do not respond to browser ‘do-not-track’ signals. You may opt-out of certain tracking, however, by disabling cookies through your browser; you also may opt-out of targeted advertising by following the instructions in the Third Party Ad Network section.

Third Party Analytics

We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate usage of our Site and, to the extent permitted, our Application. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Services. We use these tools to help us improve our Services, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. You may opt-out of Google Analytics by downloading and installing the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) for your web browser.

Third Party Ad Networks

We use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Site and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms). This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information, including Personal Information, about you.

Users in the United States may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by [DAA companies](http://www.aboutads.info/participating/). You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by [NAI members](http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating-networks).

Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or the NAI [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-based content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Site or on other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the NAI’s website at [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Children’s Privacy

Arby’s does not knowingly accept information from children under the age of 13. If we subsequently decide to offer any special promotions for this group, we will provide a Children’s Privacy Notice and will comply with all applicable laws.

Special Information for California Consumers

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at:

International User Notice

The Site is intended for use exclusively by residents of the United States of America, and our computer systems are based in the United States.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, it may be necessary for Arby’s to change this Privacy Policy. If we modify our policy, we will post the revised version here. We will also notify users who have provided us with PII about material changes to the policy if those material changes will affect the ways in which we use or disclose their already collected PII and if such notice is required by applicable law. That notice will be sent to the primary email addresses those users have provided us. Users should review this Privacy Policy periodically to be up to date on our most current privacy policies and practices.

Comments, Questions or Suggestions

If you would like to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Email: [CustomerService@arbys.com](mailto:CustomerService@arbys.com)

Mail: Arby’s Restaurant Group, Inc., 1155 Perimeter Center West, Atlanta, GA 30338
